hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermit craft and
last episode you might remember I made
this obsidian box full of lava to get
Doc well I actually bamboozled everyone
including you into thinking that this
was the trap that I had laid out for him
I had to do that because of all of these
comments look at this how is ours ever
going to be a surprise so what I'm going
to do is I'm changing it because this is
actually not the best trap even though
people like oh man Green that was those
ingenious trap that's so cool like he's
not gonna he can get out of it he has a
fire resistance potion on him so we're
going to redesign this trap because I
expect that doc will be doing some in
typical doc fashion I reckon he's gonna
be getting out the calculator doing the
math okay so if I have a fire potion I
can punch my way out of this obsidian
and blah blah blah blah it's gonna be
useless we're gonna redesign this entire
thing to explode instantly and send him
probably somewhere around there
I just need to hope he doesn't get
online also look at this mumbo-jumbo is
them he is he's dead he's dead whit
we're dead rose
I've got admit his skin does actually
looked that much different and also I've
been informed that Joe Hill's has died
as well meaning there's only a scout and
doc alive which means by default if this
is successful scale wins and dragon bros
claim the victory
so let's get this redesigned and
reconfigured and hopefully this will
work and you know I'm gonna do I mean I
don't know when Doc's gonna be online
next this is gonna hopefully not in the
next half-hour it's kind of early in the
morning so I don't think he's gonna be
awake but if we can get this done what
I'm gonna do is leave my camera account
online just to try and record this
happening so I have learnt how to make
instant exploding traps it's so easy to
do and it's pretty much 100% fatal as as
kirb has demonstrated many times during
demise the only thing that could really
go wrong here is if I truly did mess
the location but I'm pretty sure I
didn't so what I'm going to do is link
this up in theory he should I've loaded
this enough so he should fall from about
here through the string and that's going
to trigger the TNT minecart trap oh boy
here we go okay so we link these up
basically all we're gonna do is spam
some TNT minecarts on here and here he's
gonna fall through the string these two
are gonna go into each other and when
they collide kaboom and he's gonna go
straight up there I don't know if I want
to let leave this open so he goes flying
up through the tube I could do that to
be fair I don't think there's a lot he
can do if you like log in and out you
can't just suddenly fly I think I kind
of want to make him like fly up through
there but then also the TNT might yeah
I'm gonna have to protect doc space here
cuz we're kind of close to all this the
last thing I want to do is cause some
damage there so yeah I'm gonna cover
this whole thing in a box but hopefully
it'll be good and no matter what I have
tested this out on a creative world so I
know that it works I just have to
replicate my design as best I can
I learned this recently from iske
actually so thank you a scale he taught
me about this this looping thing when I
was doing my hidden house video so
season 7 here I come the time of gray
and redstone okay I think that's
basically it I've rigged it up so that
when this is once this has got the
string in it this will send it round so
let's just give it a little bit of a
test make sure and we're not gonna put
TNT on this until the very last minute
okay so let's just pretend that this is
full of TNT this is full of TNT and when
he logs in this is sunk down so when he
logs in he will log in like here boom he
goes down they go together and kaboom
and it doesn't even matter if like he he
like it touches these there'll be so
many minecart it will just be an instant
explosion it will work I hope I
absolutely hope so the last thing to do
is to seal this up in a big tube this is
to protect Doc's base because I mean all
of this
we'll get destroyed and I'll help repair
that once the damage is done but other
than that I don't want to cause any more
damage than it's strictly necessary so
that's why we're doing this so now we
need to make a bunch of tea and tea
minecarts this is the dangerous bit
because if it all goes if I do something
wrong here not only do I blow up in fact
I'm actually gonna go and put my my
valuables over here because I don't need
them right now and if I do die I don't
want to lose them now I don't know how
many tea and tea mine carts is overkill
but I reckon I reckon like six or seven
on each side that should guarantee that
he's not going anywhere once okay that's
more than enough mine carts with tea and
tea on them right so here we go one two
three four five six seven okay I'll
leave it at that
don't touch them don't touch them don't
touch them don't touch anything okay one
two three four five six seven boom no
well not boom poor choice of what seal
this up so when both of these TNT mine
carts when they get activated it's it's
just game over absolutely game over I
almost fell
alright let's seal this up before we
have an accident a very expensive
accident okay there we go
we are sorted it is done he should login
it should all go kaboom splat and then
demise will end with a bang shall we say
so that just leaves me to leave my
camera account on and see what happens I
don't know when next plans to log in
hopefully I won't end up with like 24
hours of footage but I think we can call
that job well done okay that leaves us
to tidy up and cool call it a job done I
think
I'm so sorry doc I'm pretty sure this is
there's no way out of this there might
have been a way out of the the lava trap
but not this one not this one if my
upload schedule is corrected they should
be Christmas Day or Christmas Eve and I
actually did something a little a little
Grinch abridged Grinch I did something a
little bit Grinch
now let me explain twas several weeks
before Christmas and all was quiet on
the server not a hermit was stirring no
pranks went further fall symmetry had
stopped the Secret Santa sleigh
when agreeing she logged in and sent
everything astray heard it was Christmas
and the Grinch is on to well make things
a little more interesting so we just go
into Santa's cart here bah humbug and
all that we see we've got plenty of
names who might that be
we got impulse or pretty much everyone
well let's just see what people are
going to get for Christmas ah give them
a chest full of goodies build the cute
snow globe give them a new pod a new pet
called Fred give them an igloo build a
snowman build a big Santa hat on their
base well well this just won't do won't
do everyone this year has been extra
naughty and I'm afraid they're all going
to get pranked by the Grinch
I mean degree inch but of course no one
will know until it's too late
build a big Santa hat more like a T&T
Santa hat make them a giant present more
like an elder guardian present they
won't be able to open it give them a new
pet
called Barry Ravager named Barry
decorate their base with bubbles
more like lethal bubbles give them a
chest full of goodies more like chests
full of coal there we are we have
officially it took all day but we have
officially fixed Christmas everyone has
been naughty and the chaos let the chaos
begin absolutely fabulous that's right
the Grinch has not stolen Christmas or
ruined Christmas but made Christmas a
little bit more interesting which is
where all of these ideas came from
because giving gifts at Christmas on the
hermitcraft server not know in real life
just on the hermitcraft server it's just
like you know it's cool if ITIF I got
given a snowman that's all right foot
wouldn't be more interesting if the
presents actually they did something to
your face in some ways so I thought it
was absolutely hilarious the Grinch has
taken over Secret Santa and made
everyone naughty this year and little
did everybody know except false
apparently false false must have noticed
that all of the the gifts had changed
anyway let's quickly head back to Sahara
where we've still got a little bit more
work to do I hope nothing goes wrong
with my demise trap because if that's if
that if that doesn't work then demise
continues and then we've got two sets of
people to go after doc and it's cow and
it will be a race to the grave and then
we all just need to figure out how we're
gonna end up getting back to life I
don't want to be with a black and white
skin forever okay so we are back at
Sahara and I have added a bunch of
things that we need to get and I've got
to admit there's not a lot that I can do
here this is all stuff that I think
mumbo and it's cow have all the farms
for unless I just go and take stuff from
their farms honestly there's not a lot I
can do so we're actually so close to
Christmas now as well that all of the
chests have changed too this happens
every single year and every single year
I forget they have changed to Christmas
present
which is absolutely awesome and should
be quite cool as this should go out on
Christmas Eve or Christmas Day I'm not
entirely sure I suppose I could actually
craft these are all chests I could
actually craft up some hoppers because I
did make all these chests and I mean
don't get me wrong this isn't that many
chests but this is several stacks of
logs it's really expensive to craft up a
lot of chests so maybe I can do some
hoppers just to help out a little bit
because restocking Sahara has actually
taken a whole lot longer than I ever
thought and look at that all of all of
that iron it didn't go very far so this
is gonna be another one that's yeah
probably not gonna be in high stock I
don't know and we need to stop I in as
well so that's not very good you know
I'm pretty sure someone keeps stealing
my beds by my bed anywhere just hiss
here oh hey there's there's one here but
I don't remember putting this here so a
bit of time has passed and hey guess
what doc logged in I was told shortly
after I left my camera count online and
it's happened basically and guess what
we won the trap definitely got him so
let's go into like the replay mod and
get a first-person perspective of what
just happened all right so I'm here in
the replay mod and I've just managed to
get the moment in the several hours of
footage that I got and this is the exact
moment that doc logs in as you can see
it's not triggered here at all doc has
actually logged in bang in the middle of
this so I got that absolutely spot-on
and because I dug it down he should fall
straight through here so let's just
speed take this like really slow so he's
logged in he's going to skin and OH
[Music]
he didn't even fall
he didn't even fall look you can't even
see the totem of undying particles
everywhere Wow Wow that happen he had no
chance not a single chance he had no way
of surviving that let's let's get an
instant replay of the whole thing shall
we because that was insane he said those
mine carts didn't even touch okay so
here we go this is the outside of the
box
I've actually sort of set a rendering
here to go so right you can see doc is
floating in here this is just before he
logs in and you look carefully behind
you the tripwire just triggers even
though he's nowhere near it it triggers
and he goes completely up in explosions
there's nothing he can do it triggered
before he even had control of his
character that was faster than I ever
thought possible
and it didn't even create that bad of a
mess around it either it's obviously got
some damage absolutely amazing so I
think that actually is the end of demise
if my calculations are correct and maybe
we should go over to the demise board
just to check I can't tell you how many
times I've done this journey
absolutely ridiculous I thought every
time I think that I'm done with that
area I'm going back the server is
basically split into two areas the main
island and new hermit ville which has
got all of the minigames it's got the
village it's got area 77 I mean it's
like part two of season six I guess but
I didn't expect to have to go back and
forth as much as I do
okay here we are at the demise board why
is there a tree here I mean of all the
things
okay so alive it's cow and doc I'm
afraid I'm afraid that that is no longer
the case doc has officially demised and
joined the dead team
I'm so sorry dark
but you just weren't a bro okay it's cow
congratulations on your win you survived
many many many traps you better be a bro
and split those diamonds bro you know
what I mean so all of those diamonds
they now belong to a scout of all people
and thankfully that means I can get rid
of my rubbish armor because I've died so
many times having rubbish armor and oh
wait why are chest and ender chests
exactly the same that's annoying I can
finally put my diamond armor back on
even though you're dead you were
supposed to not wear diamond armor but
it's really it's really not a big deal
at this point but what a game what a
game that was we basically played
hardcore mode without hardcore mode
which is absolutely awesome
so congratulations this guy you're the
winner maybe next episode we will set up
a big ceremony to celebrate this guy
winning and we can present him with the
Diamonds and it will be absolutely epic
so this now means that everyone is dead
we need to somehow get everyone back
alive but there's also some minigames
that I believe involve death like this
one I think this is something to do with
tango I would be really excited to play
this but it's definitely not looking
finished so maybe there's some mini
games we can play especially you know
things like ravager run like all of
those mini games that involve some kind
of minecraft death they haven't been
played so it would be awesome maybe to
have a little bit of a minigame session
because there's so many things I haven't
even tried I don't even know what half
of stuff in here is anymore I mean look
at this
speedy pines I've obviously been round
at a few times this is one of rennes
minigames but I haven't actually had a
race in it yet I mean look you just have
to appreciate how long all of this stuff
must take to make hours and hours and
hours of stuff Wow and it's sponsored by
Sahara of course which is awesome I
think Sahara sponsored the ice for this
but anyway we've still got a few minutes
left of the episode so I want to have a
quick walk and a talk with everyone
before we sign off because I really
could use your
opinion on something so as you guys know
from episode 100 the season six of
hermit craft has been absolutely amazing
and we've done so many things and in
fact we've kind of led a lot of things
as well like you know the hot potato
game tag civil war-era sense seven the
jangly all of that stuff has been a
fantastic story light and now demise as
well it's been absolutely amazing but I
have I've been asking myself the
question what's next after demise well
the answer is I don't know I just don't
know truth be told I'm kind of ready for
season seven to happen now I've got I've
got really big plans that I can only
really do in the next season of hermit
craft and that's got me pretty excited
to say the least but I've got to say I'm
feeling like I'm not sure what else to
do I mean there's probably a few more
episodes of hermit craft in this season
but the question that I want to ask is
do I keep playing season six of hermit
craft even though I feel like I don't
really know what to do I mean I can
always come up with something there's
always stuff to do it's just my my gut
feeling or do I do a short term series
that could be bit different bit fun also
multiplayer maybe on the same vibe as
hermit craft until season seven happens
and I don't know when the season 7 is
going to happen nobody knows but it's a
question that I want to ask because if
you guys love season 6 so much and you
would probably not be interested in
anything else I'll just continue season
6 I'll figure something out and I'll
make it happen but if you would like to
see another series of some kind in the
new year now is definitely the time to
tell me that as I'm really considering
what I'm going to be doing moving
forward but I mean even just flying over
this world look
how insane it is like even the Elijah
Coast I haven't done the electricals in
ages this is one of the hardest turns in
the game I always get that bit wrong oh
man I should have done them I should
have done the electricals at some point
I bet I can beat my time now but anyway
yeah let me know what you think in the
comments below but I think that is
actually going to have to be the end of
this episode and January as is for all
of YouTube maybe a little slower not
entirely sure depends what everyone
thinks in the comments to be honest with
you but I've got to say what a fantastic
year probably the best year of my life
and it's all down to you and I've got to
say a huge thank you to everyone who has
tag shopped at Sahara in real life you
guys have been absolutely amazing and
that support means absolutely everything
to me if you want to get a that ain't
brochure or a that's brochure there is
dragon bro merch officially on the
architect store for you to buy now that
will probably only be around for a few
weeks so if you love the dragon bros
consider that and we're gonna cycle
through different t-shirt designs as we
go on so it'll be probably limited
edition but I can't I can't guarantee
what exactly it's gonna be taken at the
store anyway thanks for an amazing year
everyone I hope you have a wonderful
holiday and a happy new year as well
good actually see you tomorrow there's
another video I've prepared